in the latest installment of the
Blockbuster Twitter files reporter
MattyB has revealed that probably the
most important Source behind the
maniacal media output on russiagate was
based on a lie hundreds of Articles and
television segments in the major U.S
media which kept the Russia gate Fiasco
front and center in American political
life for several years was fueled by a
website called Hamilton 68.
on Hamilton's advisory Council sits
former senior U.S officials several wood
intelligence backgrounds such as Michael
Church of former Homeland Security
director former acting CIA Chief Michael
Morrell
Rick Legend a former NSA deputy director
Clint Watts a former FBI
counterintelligence officer Mike Rogers
another former FBI agent and a member of
the U.S House intelligence committee the
former U.S ambassador to Russia Michael
mcfaul
this seems to me to be an intelligence
operation the Hamilton 68. it's only
fronted by Former Intelligence what kind
of relations do they have to current I
mean we don't have any proof obviously
but what is your speculation about
whether this was linked to people who
were actually still serving they can't
be on a board like this they can't be
seen to be involved in any of this but
they've got these former people who are
now private citizens so I just want to
know if you can weigh in on that idea
sure all former directors Deputy
directors and Associate Deputy directors
maintain their security clearances in
perpetuity
all of them are welcome to go back to
headquarters whenever they want they are
allowed classified briefings
not top secret but up to the secret
level
they have free access to the director's
private dining room in fact I've seen
them meeting in the dining room with
journalists over the years
so there's that tired old saying that
most people who are at the CIA never
really leave the CIA at that senior
level that's true because
after 30 years or 25 years all of your
contacts are in the intelligence
Community everybody's looking to make a
lot of money when they leave
and they're looking to do something new
nobody wants to make his way over to
Booz Allen and be yet another former
senior Cia person at Booz Allen there
are a million of them there they want to
do something bigger and more lucrative
and I think that's why we're seeing
these groups like Hamilton 68 pop up or
this group that that gave a red check
mark to uh Consortium news newsguard
yeah they want to do something new and
and big and more lucrative let the lower
level guys end up at Booz Allen or at
Abraxas Corporation or wherever it is
that they go now so yeah even though
they all have former in front of their
titles now
to me that doesn't really mean anything
because they have as much access
at least to people as they ever had you
know
sorry there's a political agenda here
but it wasn't just about making money I
like to ask you my dad absolutely they
make money this was an agenda to smear
Trump Wikileaks Russia and set the stage
for the crisis we've got now I think in
many ways well there there was a perfect
storm that took place you know going
back a little bit further what made John
Brennan somebody I listen I worked for
John Brennan when he was a gs-14 nobody
and what made him somebody was a deep
friendship with George Tennant and then
when it was time to retire and move on
to something else and everybody was
going either to the Hillary Clinton
campaign or to the John McCain campaign
he was literally the only senior Cia
retiree that went to the Obama campaign
and that made him somebody
he decided that he could turn that into
something even bigger
by then going to the media when he was
done you know John used to tell
everybody who would listen that he
wanted to be Secretary of Defense under
the next Democratic president well why
why would you want to make two hundred
thousand dollars as Secretary of Defense
which would then put you into your 70s
when you can spend those years at MSNBC
making
10 times
which you would have made at the
Pentagon
and then when people saw
him making money and uh what's his name
the former dni making money and every
former four-star Clapper thank you every
former four-star general is a talking
head for CNN
you know
and you've got these Democratic
credentials because you loyally
Faithfully served Barack Obama for six
years or eight years whatever it was
why not run with it and you know the the
other thing too Joe is these guys are
very very mainstream
they're very DNC there's nothing that's
going to carry them out of the
mainstream and if the mainstream is
telling them
that to beat Donald Trump you have to
chat up this DNC plan to convince the
American people that the first thing
Donald Trump does in the morning when he
wakes up is he calls his Russian Handler
to get his his marching orders for the
day
then that's what you do
it's worked for them
isn't that whole story so funny can you
imagine Donald Trump having the opsec to
keep that secret
it's just think about it a cousin of
mine who's very much a DNC you know
mover and Shaker set me up with a woman
who's an attorney at the DNC lovely
lovely woman and we went out for one
date and through the entire date all she
talked about was how the Russians
controlled Donald Trump and I said you
don't really believe that though deep
down I mean at the CIA if there was one
thing I took out of my CIA career
especially from the analytics side it's
that if you're going to say something
you absolutely have to have the
information to back it up you have to
have the facts you can't just throw a
grenade into the middle of the room and
expect everybody to salute it you have
to back it up
and she said to me I Believe In My Heart
that Donald Trump does exactly what
Vladimir Putin tells him to do
and you know I I realize there's no
sense in carrying on the conversation
any longer because they really believed
that at the DNC maybe not at that top
level that had come up with the big lie
but everybody else who was there to
implement it they believed it
something you were saying John uh it
reminded me of just the experience of
trump derangement syndrome in general
during the whole Russia gay era I mean
so this Hamilton 68 this labeling of
American citizens and other you know
ordinary people's views and expressions
of opinion as disinformation as a
Russian Bots it was just at this
hysterical pitch and I think as Matt was
also mentioning earlier it was something
that everybody experienced on kind of
like the journalist side of it but then
as you say John like when you talk to
people who really believed it it was
like a religious fervor they had about
it so I just wanted to you know ask you
all kind of about your experience of
trump derangement syndrome or what you
know that hysteria during the Russia
gate era and if that was unique I mean
or if you think this is it'll play out
the same way again on the next
equivalent narrative that the media
really pushes
I was at the Venezuelan Embassy the
night that it was ordered closed
and uh as I was leaving with most
everybody else some some elected to stay
inside I overheard two uniformed Secret
Service officers talking one of them
said so who are these people
and the other one said the ones out here
with us
the ones inside are with Putin
um and the other one kind of chuckled
and the second one said no seriously
it's like with Trump
and you know just to hear something like
that and to realize that they that they
mean it that
you know your initial reaction is you
think wow what a couple of simpletons
and then you realize no it's not that
they're simpletons it's that they've
been exposed to this propaganda for so
long this this unrelenting reporting
that that Donald Trump is a Russian
agent and that the Russians have
controlled our elections listen there's
a guy that I used to work with at the
CIA we work together desk to desk for
years
and now I just read in the Washington
Post a couple of weeks ago he was named
to head the new office of election
Integrity in the office of the Director
of National Intelligence like Integrity
for what
we've already proven that the Russians
didn't have any impact in our elections
but people really believe that they just
refuse to look at the evidence that's
placed before them we need more
reporting from the likes of Matt taibi
to prove to the American people that
they're just simply mistaken they've
been duped they've been LED astray
there's no evidence to back up what
they've been told and we have to make
sure that this doesn't happen again